{
    "title": "Histology of Skeletal Muscle",
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "1. Sarcomere is a part between:",
        "options": [
          "2A bands",
          "2 H bands",
          "2 Z bands",
          "2I bands"
        ],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "2. The contractile unit consisting of bundles of thick filaments interleaved at either end with those of thin filaments is:",
        "options": [
          "Cross bridges",
          "Sarcomere",
          "Myofibril",
          "Z band"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "3. Which of the following is false?",
        "options": [
          "Functional unit of muscle is sarcomere",
          "Actin is a thin filament",
          "The band in a myofibril is an area of thin filament",
          "Myosin is a thick filament"
        ],
        "correct": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "4. The connective tissue that surrounds individual fibers is:",
        "options": [
          "Perimysium",
          "Endomysium",
          "Epimysium",
          "Fascia"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "5. Which of the following is an invagination of the muscle cell's sarcolemma?",
        "options": [
          "T tubules",
          "Sarcoplasmic reticula",
          "Cisternae",
          "Microtubules"
        ],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "6. Which fiber type composes fast-twitch muscle?",
        "options": [
          "Intermediate fibers",
          "White fibers",
          "Red fibers",
          "None of the above",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "7. What is the connective tissue covering of a muscle fascicle?",
        "options": [
          "Endomysium",
          "Perimysium",
          "Sarcolemma",
          "Epimysium",
          "Sarcoplasm"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "8. What are the bundle of longitudinal contractile elements within a muscle cell called?",
        "options": [
          "Muscle fibers",
          "Myofibrils",
          "Myofilaments",
          "Myocardium",
          "Myosin"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "9. What is the outer connective tissue covering of the muscle?",
        "options": [
          "Sarcoplasm",
          "Perimysium",
          "Endomysium",
          "Epimysium",
          "Sarcolemma"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "10. Which fiber type has more myoglobin?",
        "options": [
          "White fibers",
          "None of the above",
          "Intermediate fibers",
          "Red fibers",
          "All of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
      },
      {
        "question": "11. Which fiber type is seen in skeletal muscle?",
        "options": [
          "All of the above",
          "Red fibers",
          "Intermediate fibers",
          "White fibers",
          "None of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "12. Endomysium is:",
        "options": [
          "Surrounds the entire muscle",
          "Surrounds each muscle fiber",
          "Surrounds the fascicles (bundles) of a muscle"
        ],
        "correct": 1
      }
    ]
  }
  
